Imagine being a child awakened in the middle of the night by a Blackhawk helicopter landing
on your roof.
Kids in Chicago are getting hit by strays.
If they see a Blackhawk land on a roof to round up bad guys, that's a dream come true.
Rib's never worried about the children before.
He thinks ice is a bigger threat than street gangs.
The whole city's infested.
We learned that the Chicago city streets have 110,000 gang members.
That's right.
They had 1,200 shootings this year alone, 360 homicides.
Parts of Chicago are more dangerous than Afghanistan.
Five percent of the people in Chicago are gang members.
Almost 10 percent of the city is illegal.
So the guard's going in.
Over 500 members of the guard from Illinois, Texas, and California have been deployed for
a 60-day mission.
And what's JB Back actually going to do about it?
Nothing.
If he tells Chicago PD to block the guard, do you think the police are loyal to Rib's
or the president?